{
    "subject": "resource/Edward_O'Brien_(Irish_republican)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/County_Wexford",
    "human_readable": "Edward O'Brien (Irish republican) was born in County Wexford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8398872017860413,
            "question": "Where was Edward O'Brien born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8021911978721619,
            "question": "In which Irish county did Edward O'Brien reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.666035532951355,
            "question": "What nationality was Edward O'Brien?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6329479813575745,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Edward O'Brien's involvement in the Irish Republican movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5373213887214661,
            "question": "Did Edward O'Brien have any connections to other prominent figures in the Irish Republican movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.527966320514679,
            "question": "What political affiliation was Edward O'Brien known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4919665455818176,
            "question": "What impact did Edward O'Brien's work have on the Irish Republican cause?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4568246901035309,
            "question": "What is known about Edward O'Brien's family background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38503265380859375,
            "question": "Were there any notable events or contributions associated with Edward O'Brien's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34744346141815186,
            "question": "Are there any primary sources or historical records that provide further details about Edward O'Brien's life and activities?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edward O'Brien (Irish republican) was born in County Wexford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_474_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable events or contributions associated with Edward O'Brien's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_474_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Edward O'Brien's family background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_474_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Edward O'Brien's work have on the Irish Republican cause?",
            "html": "dbpedia_474_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_474_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_474/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt mentions that Edward O'Brien (18 September 1974 \u00e2\u0080\u0093 18 February 1996) was a Provisional Irish Republican Army (IRA) volunteer and grew up in Gorey, County Wexford."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Edward O'Brien, who is referred to as a Provisional Irish Republican Army (IRA) volunteer, was born into a working-class family in county Wexford. This information supports the statement that Edward O'Brien (Irish republican) was born in County Wexford."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}